Hi everyone, today I will share about how to receive a UT request and analyze it.
Here is a UT request of 6865008. I take this as an example.
First, I will check if the information in the UT request is full of necessary information or not.
For example, in the C0C1 code coverage section, yes is checked, mcdc is checked, and dsd is not checked.
Thus, this test will test the code coverage and have the mcdc request.
Next is the BB and config information field.
In this test, 2 BBs are requested.
87328 and 87329.
However, here I will give an example for one BB, 87328, and the other BB will be the same.
Then, the next important information field is the information about the snapshot name or the information about the stream name.
Here, I will receive the request test for the snapshot.
And the snapshot name here has also been provided.
Next is the ASCET database.
Then, CR to provide full information.
Now, I will load the database back.
After all the testing, I will prepare a folder to load the database back.
Here, I will load the database back to this folder.
I will use the cc file.
Then, I click on the item.
After that, I will create a variable 0.03 connection.
I will select the first item.
Then, enter the user id and the password.
After that, I will search according to the information of Snapshot, select Search Jaisal Control Snapshot.
I will return to the utility press file to get the information of Snapshot name.
I will name it.
Then I will name it as Snapshot ID.
I will go to the My Source Control workspace.
I will look for the rebel that I just created.
Here.
I will load it.
This is DHC-ESP10-CV.logRule.
This process took quite a while, so I have prepared a database for it.
After loading, these components will appear in green,
as shown on the screen.
Next, I will build MTC.
Select MTC Build,
and enter the information provided in the utility request,
which is the configuration.
Next is the BB number.
I will definitely paste the BB number again.
This is it.
Now I need to build the config and the BB.
Similarly, I will build the rest of the config.
I will do the same thing.
After selecting, I will click on Start Enable Build Jobs.
This process took quite a while,
and I will open the one I have already built.
Here, it will...
This part will display the .xam,
which means it is already built successfully.
After building, I will use the required file to analyze.
That file is found in the following folder.
Go to the Database folder.
Go to Gen.
Find the successfully built config.
Select Build.
MEC.
Those two files are GenMEC.cdv
and Asket component files.
I will take those two files out.
This file is needed for the GenTPA process.
I will leave it here.
Because I have already created it.
Next, the next important step is that I have to fix the CSV file.
So that its component is similar to the FileAppRule.
I will check the CWF one time.
This time I need to fix the CSV file in the CSV folder.
In this case, I need to use this file.
Select a file named TuneOnline1.
Then here we can choose Analysis Support,
and CWF by CWF.
Then I need to return the CSV file to the CWF folder.
And then I will copy this file to the CWF folder.
Next we need to replace the polyfill of the CFPF and I will try to do the same thing on the CWF one time.
We need to take the file.
There is no much change.
First, we need to replace the CWF folder.
Next, we need to redo the Windows file.
And then we need to restore theетabiles file.
I will find the file that I want to load the database to.
I will open the open file location.
The path is correct, so I will take the path of this file.
Next is saving directory.
I will load the output after running the tool.
It is about the common file that contains the csv file just now.
Then the tool will run out of the components that have been changed to match the load rule.
At the same time, it will also create a new csv file.
Here.
I will use this new csv file and this xcat.xml file to generate TBA.
Then I will copy it through the library and I have already prepared it here.
I will turn on the TBA report generator tool.
Then I select the folder.
I will go to the folder that contains my previous two files.
Paste the snapshot link.
It is provided.
Next, select the Qt assessment yes field.
It will automatically highlight the fields that I need to load.
Here.
I will choose the csv file that was saved earlier.
This file is new.
And this xcat file.
Next.
The next important thing is this part.
I will not analyze the component rba-qbash.
So I choose exclude components.
And at the same time, I also choose exclude cpp-hpp.
Then click on generate report.
This process also takes quite a long time.
And at that time, I can get the xcat database.
I will use the xcat database link provided in the previous request utility.
Here.
I will take that link.
Go to TCM on the computer.
Paste it here.
Then.
I will copy.
I will cut the version.
The second number of it.
25.3.
And.
Here.
It is correct.
25.3.
Then.
So I will take this xcat database and copy it to my local.
I have prepared all these files.
Ok.
After generating.
File tba.
Then it will look like this.
Internal report snapshot.
Then.
I will turn this file on.
Ok.
Ok fine.
Remove.
Okay.
For empty verdict, I will usually use testUT for the undefined modules here.
For unnecessary modules, I will hide them again.
Basically, I will analyze for these modules.
I usually paste a template here.
Then I will use tool to check.
That's all.
Thank you for watching.
See you next time.
Bye for now.
I will test the database and the file that I have just changed the format of it.
Then, after running, I click Execute.
After running, I will get a file like this.
I have prepared this before.
The file will be like this.
I will click Execute.
OK.
Here, I will put it in the item name and concat column.
The concat column is an important column so that I can accurately check whether that module has been tested or not.
And...
In this column, I will concat between...
For example, like module C, it will be the name, item name and checking date.
As for ESP, it will be item name and item revision.
Here, I have put the formula for it.
Apply the formula for it.
As I said earlier,
I will check the undefined modules.
And here, usually, I will check the ESP modules first.
So that these two modules will not be used.
OK.
For the ESP modules,
it is possible that it has been tested.
And it is tested by Candata.
So, in the empty verdict, it is now undefined.
I will check it by checking the database file.
Here.
In the database file, it will show the items that have been tested.
At the same time, with the corresponding commands.
In the B column.
In this stage, only VNUC-COP is used.
VNUC-COP.
In this column.
And...
For example,
As shown on the screen, some items have already been tested because this module has been tested by the data channel and deleted the result to TCM, so the result is that C0 and C1 are displayed here.
So I don't need to test these modules anymore.
Ok, I will log in for it.
And in the Empty Netted module, I will hit it again.
Ok, for the rest, I will delete it.
Ok, done.
In this module,
there is a problem.
I have removed the item list here, so I will paste it back in the data channel.
This is the result after running TCM just now.
Here.
Ah.
I will select the item list that is in the SketchDatabase.v.
Here, I will select this item list.
There.
Then, the tool will help me fill in the information of that module.
Ah.
In this step,
after filling in,
the second step is the same.
Ok, I will click here.
Ok.
Ok, I will fill in the information.
Ok, I will copy it back for the ESV modules.
Ok.
For the modules such as Parameter Class, Message Class, or Hierarchical,
I will not test them.
I will valid them.
Ok.
First of all, there are these modules, then we will load it out
This is the page
The link is valid
And what about the rest?
I will check the rest
Among the modules that I can run, this module is hierarchical
I will check again to see if it is correct by checking each module here
With the database that I can load back
I will check this module
Select
Yes, it is hierarchical class
Then I will comment here
This module, in the hierarchical form, will be valid or not tested
Then
OK
I have also searched and checked those modules.
Here, in addition to the module that has just been released, there is also this module.
It is also a high-radical type.
Check it out here.
OK. I will type it in.
And it is valid.
This is correct. This is also correct.
For the rest of the modules, I will analyze based on ELOCK.
Then, in ELOCK, I haven't checked it yet.
I haven't received the yellow information.
Then, I also have the modules that haven't been analyzed yet.
OK.
Then, I will use the tool Cmetrix to get the ELOCK number.
Then, I will use the tool Cmetrix to get the ELOCK number of the modules in the database.
Then, after turning Cmetrix on, it will help me.
I click on the plus sign.
I paste the yellow database into the yellow database.
Then, I press the OK button.
After Cheryl sex on, I press the OK button.
Okay.
I press the OK button.
Here, I have the ELOCK results in her request.
Next, I'll press this button to analyze,
A-N-A-L-I-ZE
.
Then I press D,
When the ELOCK object has run,
Press the station.
I click View Output File Metric
I will save the current result about my database
My workspace
Click Save
After that
I import to this File TBA to analyze
Here, my File Metric
Then
And at the same time
I will also build MTC
I will build MTC Tools
That is, build the necessary modules for File C
I will choose each File C
Then I will take all these modules
Here
I will give
Analyze the list of modules here
This process
Because this process takes a long time
So I will build
Let the tool run along with the analyze process
To save more time
Then
After getting the information here
Then next is I will use Tool
MTC Tools just now
I will open this file
config.xml
Here
I will load the file
MTC
MTC Output
Here
And there is a small trick
I will load the line from the bottom to the top
For the information
In this part
And at the top
Of the file
I will load
The other line
The word Batch
To load
Because the MTC button has been detected
And the other steps have not yet
So I will load the other Batch
To load and build
For me
I will find the MTC file
That output in
The Gen object
I will return to the database
Select
Select Gen
Then
I will go to find
Configure just now
Exactly
Here
Select Build
This is the file after
MTC successfully
I have this file
I choose
Batch Copy
Then I will load the corresponding
In
I will load the information
Down here
Then I will go upside down
Up
Up Up
And note that I will zip the database just now
The database I logged back
Here I have also zipped
Here I will see the page of it
Fill in here
Then List of Modules
I have also zipped
I will fill in here
Then
After filling in all the information
I will go to mcdctool.bat
Run the tool
After running the tool, it will come out
This item
Name, Database
And the number of BBs that I just ran
See
After running the tool, it will come out a file for me
This TBA file
This file will have the information to help me
Skype
After the test is done, it will be easier
As well as
Other information
I will take the information here
Then I also put it in the file
Analysis
Here I set it to Toolprint
I will leave it here
Then go back to the TBA file just now
Then
I will boot
I will find the in-log
For the modules that need to be tested here
I will go back to the TBA file
Then
So
Here
I will use VLOOKUP
Item Name
And
Grammetric
3 important database information
It is
It's effect
C
Next is a
A
Now
A function
Is a
Max
Easy
Ok
Function
I'm kind of Ok
Will apply to all the models here
Ok
Okay, first of all, I have a table like this.
Then, after having the ilog information here,
I will check again that for the C modules,
which module has the function equal to 0,
which means there is no function,
which means I will make a list,
then no, it doesn't exist here.
Then, I will do as usual.
Tune helps me to collect the information
that has been tested before or not,
and at the same time, I will also go to check
whether it has been tested in recent years or not.
Ah.
OK.
Then, I have also built a formula for this.
Then, I will show you the formula here.
Here.
My formula is to check again with the TestedDatabase file.
The TestedDatabase file.
This file here.
This file.
Ah. This file.
Here.
OK.
Then, I will check that the test is done.
Here, I will check whether that module has been tested
by, ah, has been tested by, ah,
by Candata or G-Test,
or is tested.
Then, there is only one, ah,
if it has been, ah,
and it will give the final test environment here.
For that module, if it is a C module, it will be tested by Kanata or G-Test.
And if it is an ASW module, an ISP module, here, Atomsize ISP, then it will be tested by G-Test.
Then, this node, MTnit, is the display node for testing that module.
If it is already tested, it will be marked as Delta.
And it will also calculate the effort for Delta.
Here, I will apply it to all the items here.
Do you understand?
If you have questions, please send your inquiries.
And this module is for testing
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
I'm a bit laggy
I have checked all the necessary information here
If the module has not been tested, it will be new in this anti-nit-nit node
However, this tab has already been tested, so my FILE TEXTED DATABASE has been updated appropriately
This means that most of the modules in the anti-nit-nit node are all delta
Next, I will calculate the effort according to ELOCK
From there, I will calculate the total effort for that module based on the effort according to ELOCK and the state of delta or new
The test will end here
To calculate quickly, I have already written a formula for this
Then paste it in here
If I type Valid here, if the module is C, it will be 0.1
And I will check the test environment here
If the module is C, it will be tested according to the test, then it will calculate another ELOCK
And if it is tested according to the test, it will calculate another ELOCK
And similarly for ASCII
If it is ESP, it will calculate according to the formula of ASCII
Then
And here is the delta, so it is
The total effort will be equal to
It will be equal to this times 0.4
And because the minimum effort for a module is 0.6
So my formula is 0.6 here
Then
I will apply it to all the items here
OK
Then
the
Let's start here
One more time
I'm not sure for it, I'm not sure for it, if you want to get it, I'll
count it as 0.05, this is this, and so on, ok, ok,
ok,
To make it more beautiful, I will make it look like a cloud.
After that, I will check the information in the Basically Filter.
I will check it again.
After that, I will check the mode undefined to see if I have analyzed enough for all of them.
I have checked all of them.
For the C modules, I will list them separately.
I will fill in the CECFCG columns to make it easier for the tester to install after they have finished.
I will also use Reboot Cup.
And this one.
And for the button part, I will get the result from the MCDCTool.
MCDCTool.com.
This is the result.
Now, I will look up.
I will look up.
Atom name.
And...
Wait a minute.
OK.
It looks fine.
And finally, we have a question.
OK.
I will go back to my desk for a while.
There are no questions.
I will pick up their questions.
I will choose to do it again.
Then...
Thank you for watching.
OK, that's right, I'll apply it to all of them here, OK, so I've done the analysis,
then I'll go back to Samurai, here there are 51 items that need to be tested, and 12 items that need to be valid.
Here, I'll go back to Samurai, and here there are 51 items that need to be tested, and 12 items that need to be valid.
As for bmp873428, it will have 63 items which need perform UC, and in that there are 12 items that need to be valid and 51 items that need to be tested.
For.I will...
For this file, I will create another estimation file, to send to xia.
I will save it as a file
Estimation
OK
In this file, I will give it
all values, not the formula
I will save the elog
anti-command, anti-nitid
and total effort
for a module
undefined
I will go and fill in the undefined modules
Here
I will remove these
too
OK
Basically, it's done
1 task
So
Like
OK